classworks.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Classworks

##  Privacy Policy 

Curriculum Advantage, Inc. knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Curriculum Advantage, Inc. website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers Curriculum Advantage, Inc.'s treatment of personal information that Curriculum Advantage, Inc. gathers when you are on the Curriculum Advantage, Inc. website and when you use Curriculum Advantage, Inc. services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Curriculum Advantage, Inc. does not own or control, or to individuals that Curriculum Advantage, Inc. does not employ or manage.

## Information Collected by Curriculum Advantage, Inc.

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our Curriculum Advantage, Inc. users:

### Information You Provide to Us

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

### Registration

In order for you to use Curriculum Advantage, Inc. services, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require select personal information (including your full name, city, state and e-mail address).

### Automatic Information

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Curriculum Advantage, Inc. and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, Curriculum Advantage, Inc. cookie information, and the page you requested. Curriculum Advantage, Inc. uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website. Curriculum Advantage, Inc. may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Curriculum Advantage, Inc. will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

### E-mail Communications

Curriculum Advantage, Inc. is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the "Sharing Your Information" section below. Curriculum Advantage, Inc. may send out e-mails with Curriculum Advantage, Inc.-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. You may also receive notification e-mails from Curriculum Advantage, Inc., which inform you of actions that have been performed on the site. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please send an email to remove@classworks.com. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us.

### Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Curriculum Advantage, Inc. cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of Curriculum Advantage, Inc.'s features.

## Sharing Your Information

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.

### Curriculum Advantage, Inc. Personnel

Curriculum Advantage, Inc. personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of Curriculum Advantage, Inc. business.

### Business Transfers

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Curriculum Advantage, Inc., or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.

### Protection of Curriculum Advantage, Inc. and Others

We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Curriculum Advantage, Inc., our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Syndication

Curriculum Advantage, Inc. allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the Curriculum Advantage, Inc. website.

### With Your Consent

Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.

### Enabling Third-Party Integrations

If you enable a third-party integration service to work with Classworks, such as an LMS, that third-party may collect information on its own through the use of its integration with Classworks. Collection and use of information in this way is governed by the privacy policies of the third-party and is beyond our control.

Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as Curriculum Advantage, Inc. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit the third-party website, you should read that site's privacy statement before providing any personally identifiable information or enabling the Classworks integration.

## Keeping Information Secure

Your Curriculum Advantage, Inc. account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices.

### Ways to Control Display and Use of Your Information

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, but then you may be unable to use certain features on our website. You may request deletion of your Curriculum Advantage, Inc. account by e-mailing us at remove@classworks.com. However, please note that you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us.

As explained earlier, the "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our features.

### The Children’s Internet Protection Act

The Children’s Internet Protection Act (CIPA) is a federal law enacted by Congress in December 2000 to address concerns about access to offensive content over the Internet on school and library computers. CIPA imposes certain types of requirements on any school or library that receives funding support for Internet access or internal connections from the “E-rate” program — a program that makes certain technology more affordable for eligible schools and libraries. Our Programs do not provide links to external resources or chat rooms, and do not contain any offensive or inappropriate material. If you would like more information about CIPA, please go to http://www.fcc.gov/cgb/consumerfacts/cipa.html.

### The Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act

The Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) is a Federal law that protects the privacy of student education records. The law applies to all schools that receive funds under an applicable program of the U.S. Department of Education. If you would like more information about FERPA, please go to http://www.ed.gov/policy/gen/guid/fpco/ferpa/index.html.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Curriculum Advantage, Inc. may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on http://status.classworks.com so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed. We recommend subscribing to updates by clicking on the Subscribe to Updates button and you will receive notice of any updates in your email.

### Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit the Classworks or any Curriculum Advantage, Inc. website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and the application of Georgia state law.

### Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 16, 2014.
